<root>
	<giveaway>
		<title>Apple iPhone 15</title>
		<short>Experience the future in your palm with the all-new Apple iPhone 15! Get ready to elevate your mobile experience with cutting-edge technology, stunning design, and unparalleled performance. Enter now for a chance to win this revolutionary device and stay ahead of the curve!</short>
		<website>https://www.google.com/</website>
		<thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ninonur/cpagrip/main/assets/Apple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-two-Nano-SIM-IP68-CN-version-Brand-new-and-inactive-original.png_.webp</thumbnail>
	</giveaway>
	<giveaway>
		<title>Apple iPhone 14</title>
		<short>Unlock endless possibilities with the sleek and powerful Apple iPhone 14! From its breathtaking display to its lightning-fast processor, this device is designed to keep up with your every need. Don't miss your chance to own the latest innovation in mobile technology. Enter our giveaway now!</short>
		<website>https://www.google.com/</website>
		<thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ninonur/cpagrip/main/assets/Apple-iPhone-14-plus-two-Nano-SIM-IP68-CN-version-Brand-new-and-inactive-original-genuine.jpg_.webp</thumbnail>
	</giveaway>
	<giveaway>
		<title>Apple AirPods Pro</title>
		<short>Immerse yourself in pure audio bliss with the Apple AirPods Pro! Featuring active noise cancellation, customizable fit, and superior sound quality, these earbuds redefine the way you experience music and calls. Enter to win a pair and elevate your listening experience to new heights!</short>
		<website>https://www.google.com/</website>
		<thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ninonur/cpagrip/main/assets/MTJV3_AV2.jpg</thumbnail>
	</giveaway>
	<giveaway>
		<title>Apple AirPods 2</title>
		<short>Enjoy wireless freedom like never before with the Apple AirPods 2! Seamlessly connect to all your devices, experience crystal-clear sound, and stay effortlessly connected throughout your day. Enter now for a chance to win these iconic earbuds and take your audio experience to the next level!</short>
		<website>https://www.google.com/</website>
		<thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ninonur/cpagrip/main/assets/MQD83.jpg</thumbnail>
	</giveaway>
	<giveaway>
		<title>MacBook Pro 16</title>
		<short>Unleash your creativity and productivity with the powerhouse that is the MacBook Pro 16"! Featuring stunning Retina display, lightning-fast performance, and all-day battery life, this laptop is your ultimate tool for work and play. Enter our giveaway today and elevate your computing experience with the MacBook Pro 16!</short>
		<website>https://www.google.com/</website>
		<thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ninonur/cpagrip/main/assets/236492_MacBook_Pro_16__2023__AKrales_0114.jpg</thumbnail>
	</giveaway>
 </root>
